I don't know.
I can't forget this.
The Rinoa University of Magic dormitories.
For several years now, this has been my home.
Every morning, I wake up, wash my face, and go for a run around Sharia, the City of Magic, until I feel like I can't run anymore.
It's helped me memorize the layout of the city streets, and made me more aware of my own physical limitations.
No one really recommended this routine to me, per se, but it's always felt like something Rudy might do, if he were in my position.
Classes are boring. They mostly just retread things I learned from Rudy, which goes to show just how much he knew about magic, I guess.
How exactly does this type of magic work?
Oh, of course. You know when you have a red-hot rock or stone? Dropping it in water will make it steam? It's kind of like that.
Ah, I see. Her Highness is eager to learn. I tend to prefer dedicated, positive people like her. Maybe I have Rudy to thank for that.
Ooh, I never knew there was a path through here. I found it recently. It's a shortcut to the boutique.
There's something charming about it, despite how winding and narrow it is.
It must be a remnant of when the city was first constructed. The older districts are maze-like by design, because the city's location was so vulnerable to invasion.
Oh, wow. I didn't think you took your lessons seriously, but listen to you. I guess you do pay attention.
No, I picked that up from a girl I went out with.
Good thing playing the field hasn't stabbed you in the back yet.
What will be, will be. I do have Noto's blood running in my veins.
Noto's blood, huh? Rudy comes from that same family, right?
He must be a ladies' man himself, then. I wonder if he would keep skirt-chasing even if he was married to someone.
He probably would. His father did it.
Huh.
Rudy. Ugh.
Almost feels like he's all I ever want to think about anymore.
I just don't know what we are to each other.
What should I do?
It can't be a person without a person than a child.
iston of my husband, be conjunct me.
I need to bring it to someone.
It can be done when I'm gonna leave my child.
But I think they have the connection to this.
I'm gonna take the rest.
I know where I'm up to this house.
I'm going to try again.
I'm going to look up the house, but not be I think I want to stay on our family.
I'm stroomed in myorpom並 twelve mine career.
I mean, you know, I love this house.
I'm going toาน how young people use as hair anyway.
I usually describe a music that kind ofgehs when a student is and good for it.
A month has passed since Julie arrived. I assigned her training exercises as an
experiment. I let her use one incantation to start the day, but then I have her
focus on conjuring lumps of clay without speaking at all. Zanoba was under the
impression that she'd never learned silent spell casting that way, but she
pulled it off in under a month. She knew a handful of human words already and likes
mimicking others. She's just a really smart girl, and I thought figures were all
Zanoba cared about, but he's been taking great care of her, too. Most slaves, once
they're bought, are branded or marked with an enchantment that keeps them from
escaping, but I didn't like the idea of that. Julie isn't a slave. She's my
apprentice and practically a sister to Zanoba. Then one day, disaster struck.
Listen up, Julie! No great work is possible without passion. So as our
master's first disciple, I, Zanoba, shall recount the wonders of his artistic
fervor. Tonight we shall focus on the Ruizured figure. Behold this dreadful and
mighty warrior. He never loses his luster. Upon first glance, I'm sure you'll agree
the most striking feature of this work is in arguably its pose.
That reminds me. Whatever happened to the Raxi figurine?
Powered dragon also a powerful sadness.
Oh, that? Well, I, I left it back in Chiron, of course. Liar.
Actually, I do have it here, in a sense. Do you really? Would you get it out? I'd love
to see it again. It's been forever.
Hey, what the hell happened?
Explain yourself, Zanoba. When did, what did you, what the hell is going on?
You know how devoted I am to my master, don't you? How much I revere her, honor her.
I bored every ounce of my loyalty into this figure. And for it to wind up like this...
Zanoba, this is an affront to my master and my goddess. So, are you actually my enemy?
Perish the thought!
Please understand, I was challenged to a duel and I...
A duel, you say?
Yes. Minya and Persina challenged me to one during my first year here.
Ah, those two Doldia girls, yes?
Before we began, we each had to wager something precious to us.
And I...
Forgive me, my master!
I lost!
It's not your fault.
No, sir. Thank you.
But you should have told me what happened much sooner, my dear pupil.
I wouldn't have tried to ingratiate myself with those brutes if you had.
How dare they? How dare they take someone else's hard work and destroy it like that?
They will pay.
This is like smashing someone's PC with a bat.
Damn them.
Those assholes will get no mercy from me.
What do you say we teach them a lesson?
Uh, okay, yes sir!
If you keep making us late to dinner, I'm just gonna stop waiting for you.
No, give it a rest already, you pig.
Ugh.
What are Mew looking at, weirdos?
Linia. Smells like they're itching for a fight.
Xanobah, you're not really asking for another duel.
I can't believe the scrawny looking first year is who you want backing you up against us too, meow.
Hmph!
That does it! The gloves are coming off, meow!
Didn't think you would want your other stupid little doll to get all trampled on too!
Pfff!
Master, please allow me to...
No, no, it's fine. They're the ones who should be embarrassed.
Always attached at the hip, ganging up on whomever they feel like at the time.
You know? It's almost like they want everyone to know they can't do anything alone.
What did you say?
Better watch it, new kid. You're on thin ice with that attitude.
Just shut up and stay in your corner and we can leave each other alone.
But keep yapping like that and I'll destroy Mew.
Anyway, go let all that sink in.
We're busy honor students and we have way better things to do than argue with children like Mew.
Pick a fight with someone else, meow.
Why do you still Mew like a baby?
The beast folk I know all speak like adults, but I guess that's beyond you.
Jackass.
I'll strip you naked and splash water on you!
Ugh, you really do have a short fuse.
Hey, grab Prisina!
Ah!
Went with white today.
Whoa!
So tall but so slow.
Ah!
What?
What the?
Ah!
Okay.
Julie?
Superb work as always, Master.
You didn't need my help at all, did you?
Yeah.
I kinda surprised myself actually.
I expected more from them.
Guess that means Paul and Eris were both way stronger than I thought.
Oh!
Rise and shine, ladies!
Where do we even begin with you two?
Oh!
I wonder if this is what'll cure the old you-know-what.
Nope.
They're nice, but I still don't feel anything.
Not even a peep from the little guy.
Guess I can't count on the gray rat predilections too much.
Oh, well.
Master, uh, is that the sort of punishment you had in mind for them?
Oh, no.
Just a little experiment.
Now then, no games, please.
Do you understand why you're in this predicament?
Uh-uh.
I'm pretty sure we haven't done anything to you.
Oh!
You haven't, have you?
Hmph.
This is your handiwork, is it not?
Uh-uh.
It appears in this creepy taken sketch, like the deadly,
What does that creepy doll have to do with it?
That figure is modeled after my goddess.
Your goddess?
That's correct.
The one to whom I owe my ability to go out and experience the world.
I created that figure in the very image of my deity.
And you, in cold blood, smashed it to pieces.
So, girls, what do you have to say for yourselves?
I'm not the one who stomped on it!
That was all Lydia!
I told her to stop and she kept going!
This'll be fun.
You said it was creepy and ugly, so you didn't want it!
Yeah, but you still stomped on it!
Whatever! My foot slipped!
Plus, you're the one who kicked all the pieces apart across the courtyard, meow!
Silence! You are equally responsible!
And heretics must be punished!
That said, my religion is newly established, so I haven't yet determined the penalties for such cases.
But, well, don't try anything funny or else my dad and grandpa will have something to say and meowdit!
Oh, do you mean Gaius?
Yes, that takes me back.
He once falsely accused me of a crime.
He said I'd done something reprehensible to the tribe's sacred beast.
So, in return, I was stripped naked, doused with water, and dumped in a cell.
Shall I do the same thing to you?
What?!
No! No, please anything but that! I'll do whatever you say, meow!
I don't care what happens to Lidia! Just spare me! I beg you!
Absolutely! I don't care what happens to me! Just me!
The Doldia tribe can be quite ruthless when it comes to their sacred beast, as I'm sure you're aware.
Now, they did apologize when they realized they were mistaken.
But in this case, there's no question of guilt!
We didn't know. Please forgive us! We won't do it again, okay?
You bet your ass you won't.
If you want my forgiveness, then put this figure back together like it was!
Rock! See! Rock! See! Rock! See!
Rock! See! Rock! See! Rock! See! Rock! See!
Do you see it now? Rock! See! Do you see it now?
Not even my master can repair it!
Roxy!
No, this is totally fixable.
Roxy! Roxy! Roxy! Roxy!
I've got all the parts, and I've improved since I first made it.
Roxy! Roxy! Roxy! Roxy! Roxy! Roxy! Roxy! Roxy!
Well, now what?
Roxy! Roxy! Roxy!
So now I'm kind of stuck, I guess.
Uh, I'm sorry. Uh, go back. Um, you're saying you and Xanaba have them bound and locked in your room?
Oh, I think I gave him the wrong idea.
They are in my room, but I didn't try to sleep with them or anything.
Ah, is that so?
Well, I guess I did touch one of their breasts.
Y-you touched their breasts?
Yeah, but I just wanted to check something.
So, uh, you did touch them, but not like that?
Nope, that was never the plan.
Oh, okay.
In any case, I could use your wisdom on how to handle this now.
I want to punish them in some way, but the lesson has to stick.
And I don't want to incur their wrath and leave them seeking revenge down the line.
You got any ideas?
That's a tough needle to thread.
Mmm.
Okay. I have just the thing.
Oh.
We are rapidly approaching famous last words territory, but whatever, I trust him.
Do your worst, creep. I ain't scared of you.
Only, if you're gonna keep us locked up in here, you could at least uncover our hands, meow.
Being tied up is the worst, meow.
I promise we won't run away.
Yeah, he'll be good too.
Come on, just feed me already.
I'll stop howling in the dorm at night.
I won't beg teachers anymore.
I'm begging to get me a snack.
I'm dying over here.
Come on, we should...
Okay, fine. I'll do whatever you say, but nothing that results in babies, meow.
I want to date someone and get married before I do any of that. Are we clear?
Same for me.
But you can still touch Lenya's boobs every now and then if you want.
Yeah, meow. You can still...
Wait! Why only mine?
Mine aren't cheap. You're gonna give me the good steak for that.
Mine aren't cheap either, meow!
Anyway, boss, you gonna let us go or what?
I'm boss now?
I really am hungry. I have some jerky in my room and I can smell it from here.
Yeah, meow. You realize we haven't had anything to eat or drink since last night.
I don't like her tone.
You don't sound sorry enough.
Fitz? It's none of your business, meow.
No kidding. No ni-nya.
Oh, that does it! Girls, set!
My apologies, Master Fitz. You may continue.
This is gonna be fun.
Hey. There's a tribe on the demon continent that uses this paint to mark their bodies when they come of age.
The right incantation will melt the markings into your skin permanently.
I won't forget this any time soon, Fitz.
No ni-yo.
If you ever disobey Rudeus, I'll cast the spell the second you do, and you will wear that shame forever!
Master Fitz doesn't pull any punches.
You'll keep your faces like this at school tomorrow. And then I'll remove the paint.
Hey, boss. You knocked us out in the courtyard real fast. How could you track us so well?
I really just remembered my training and acted accordingly.
Meow, who was your master?
Oh. Um... I guess Ghislaine.
Our Ghislaine? As in Ghislaine of the Doldia tribe. Sword King Ghislaine.
Oh, yeah. Of course her.
That's right. If Linia is Gaius' daughter, obviously that means Ghislaine is her aunt.
That makes sense.
Be seeing, Mew.
See you later, boss. I'm sorry again about your perv doll.
Good grief.
Um, hey, Rudeus. That wasn't too far, right?
I don't think so. But you mentioned a special incantation for that paint.
If anyone else knows it, we could all be in big trouble.
Huh? Oh, uh, that was a lie. Sorry?
That was just regular cheap paint you use for magic circles.
Little Mana will wash it off.
Hey, I've been curious since I walked in. What might that be?
Oh, yeah. I keep a holy relic of my faith in it.
Really? Then you're not a follower of Millis?
No, sir. I'm a lifelong Roxy-
Would you mind if I take a li- No, no, please don't open it!
Sorry.
The shock may be more than Master Fitz can handle.
But, uh, yeah. Make yourself at home, otherwise.
You weren't joking. This pillow does rattle. Can I put my head on it?
Go ahead.
This is really comfy.
He even keeps the glasses on when he lies down. What would happen if I reached over and just took them off?
Wanna see?
To see what?
My whole face.
Yeah, I do.
Uh, I'm just kidding. I can't. Under Princess Ariel's orders, I'm actually forbidden to show my face at all.
Oh, I didn't know. Well, I won't try to force you then.
I appreciate it. But speaking of Her Highness, I guess I had better be going.
Sure. Thank you for everything.
Yeah, you're welcome. And, uh, good night.
Uh, good night.
What would have happened if I had seen Fitz's face just now?
For some reason, I feel like that would have been a point of no return.
La-ya-la-ya-la